naijasay.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy policy – NaijaSay

This privacy policy page is to enlighten you on how we collect data from you and what exactly we use this data for, we will try to explain ecerything to the best of our ability.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you comment on our site, contact us or fill any form

What do we use your information for?

We use these information to:

  * **To improve our website**

We continually strive to improve what we offer on thus website based on the information and feedback we receive from the data we collected from you.

This information better help us in addressing you and help to serve you even more better

  * To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support.

  * To process transactions

Consider your information safe with us as they will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of offering the best service we have to offer to you

  * To send Newsletter

This email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. We also use them to send daily newletter to your blog every day if you optioned for this as you can choose to disable them anytime you like.

This newsletter is better used to send you our latest updates on naijasay, you can have it all with naijasay. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes of course! (Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser when you surf the net and it also enables the websites to easily recognize your browser and capture or remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about estimated site traffic and site interaction and we may choose to collect your ip address so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may need to release your information when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. Lawful steps will be taken before we embark on this and you must be proven guilty.

## Third party links and ad-network policy like adsense

Occasionally, at our volition, we may choose to include or offer third party products or services on our website like affiliate marketing and adsense etc.

These third party ad-networks or companies have their separate and independent privacy policies and We therefore have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content and activities of these linked sites we serve ads from.

We may decide to use adsense ad network in future and this is their privacy policy page on ad served : <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites so if you find any of these websites guilty of any sort, please don’t hesitate to contact us at contact@naijasay.com.

## Seeking Your Consent

By using our site, it shows that you consent to our website (blog) privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

In the future, If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so we will admonish you to refresh this page from time to time but before we do this we will make sure you aren’t affected in any way.

If there is any question regarding this privacy policy page or you want to know more on information collected from you, you may contact us through the following lik <http://naijasay.com/contact-us/>
